[
    {
        "question": "適切",
        "answer": "てきせつ"
    },
    {
        "question": "才能",
        "answer": "さいのう"
    },
    {
        "question": "面",
        "answer": "めん"
    },
    {
        "question": "消費",
        "answer": "しょうひ"
    },
    {
        "question": "方法",
        "answer": "ほうほう"
    },
    {
        "question": "飛び出す",
        "answer": "とびだす"
    },
    {
        "question": "機械",
        "answer": "きかい"
    },
    {
        "question": "地位",
        "answer": "ちい"
    },
    {
        "question": "位",
        "answer": "くらい"
    },
    {
        "question": "迷惑",
        "answer": "めいわく"
    },
    {
        "question": "住宅",
        "answer": "じゅうたく"
    },
    {
        "question": "係",
        "answer": "かかり"
    },
    {
        "question": "上等",
        "answer": "じょうとう"
    },
    {
        "question": "記事",
        "answer": "きじ"
    },
    {
        "question": "真っ直ぐ",
        "answer": "まっすぐ"
    },
    {
        "question": "変更",
        "answer": "へんこう"
    },
    {
        "question": "納得",
        "answer": "なっとく"
    },
    {
        "question": "数",
        "answer": "かず"
    },
    {
        "question": "悲劇",
        "answer": "ひげき"
    },
    {
        "question": "合わせる",
        "answer": "あわせる"
    },
    {
        "question": "痛み",
        "answer": "いたみ"
    },
    {
        "question": "相手",
        "answer": "あいて"
    },
    {
        "question": "化粧",
        "answer": "けしょう"
    },
    {
        "question": "成長",
        "answer": "せいちょう"
    },
    {
        "question": "組む",
        "answer": "くむ"
    },
    {
        "question": "覚悟",
        "answer": "かくご"
    },
    {
        "question": "最中",
        "answer": "さいちゅう"
    },
    {
        "question": "批判",
        "answer": "ひはん"
    },
    {
        "question": "貧しい",
        "answer": "まずしい"
    },
    {
        "question": "国民",
        "answer": "こくみん"
    },
    {
        "question": "絵画",
        "answer": "かいが"
    },
    {
        "question": "出席",
        "answer": "しゅっせき"
    },
    {
        "question": "直に",
        "answer": "じかに"
    },
    {
        "question": "見解",
        "answer": "けんかい"
    },
    {
        "question": "骨折",
        "answer": "こっせつ"
    },
    {
        "question": "宅",
        "answer": "たく"
    },
    {
        "question": "費用",
        "answer": "ひよう"
    },
    {
        "question": "回り",
        "answer": "まわり"
    },
    {
        "question": "老い",
        "answer": "おい"
    },
    {
        "question": "積もる",
        "answer": "つもる"
    },
    {
        "question": "程度",
        "answer": "ていど"
    },
    {
        "question": "同様",
        "answer": "どうよう"
    },
    {
        "question": "期間",
        "answer": "きかん"
    },
    {
        "question": "散歩",
        "answer": "さんぽ"
    },
    {
        "question": "気付く",
        "answer": "きづく"
    },
    {
        "question": "欠陥",
        "answer": "けっかん"
    },
    {
        "question": "支給",
        "answer": "しきゅう"
    },
    {
        "question": "知識",
        "answer": "ちしき"
    },
    {
        "question": "番",
        "answer": "ばん"
    },
    {
        "question": "ジェット機",
        "answer": "ジェットき"
    },
    {
        "question": "相続",
        "answer": "そうぞく"
    },
    {
        "question": "増加",
        "answer": "ぞうか"
    },
    {
        "question": "途端",
        "answer": "とたん"
    },
    {
        "question": "熱帯",
        "answer": "ねったい"
    },
    {
        "question": "末",
        "answer": "すえ"
    },
    {
        "question": "実験",
        "answer": "じっけん"
    },
    {
        "question": "交換",
        "answer": "こうかん"
    },
    {
        "question": "似合う",
        "answer": "にあう"
    },
    {
        "question": "普段",
        "answer": "ふだん"
    },
    {
        "question": "老人",
        "answer": "ろうじん"
    },
    {
        "question": "疑問",
        "answer": "ぎもん"
    },
    {
        "question": "科目",
        "answer": "かもく"
    },
    {
        "question": "皆",
        "answer": "みんな"
    },
    {
        "question": "愛",
        "answer": "あい"
    },
    {
        "question": "指導",
        "answer": "しどう"
    },
    {
        "question": "育つ",
        "answer": "そだつ"
    },
    {
        "question": "列",
        "answer": "れつ"
    },
    {
        "question": "芝居",
        "answer": "しばい"
    },
    {
        "question": "面倒",
        "answer": "めんどう"
    },
    {
        "question": "招く",
        "answer": "まねく"
    },
    {
        "question": "確認",
        "answer": "かくにん"
    },
    {
        "question": "対する",
        "answer": "たいする"
    },
    {
        "question": "失業",
        "answer": "しつぎょう"
    },
    {
        "question": "正式",
        "answer": "せいしき"
    },
    {
        "question": "議長",
        "answer": "ぎちょう"
    },
    {
        "question": "節約",
        "answer": "せつやく"
    },
    {
        "question": "便",
        "answer": "びん"
    },
    {
        "question": "努力",
        "answer": "どりょく"
    },
    {
        "question": "素晴らしい",
        "answer": "すばらしい"
    },
    {
        "question": "宝石",
        "answer": "ほうせき"
    },
    {
        "question": "化学",
        "answer": "かがく"
    },
    {
        "question": "受け取る",
        "answer": "うけとる"
    },
    {
        "question": "帰宅",
        "answer": "きたく"
    },
    {
        "question": "権利",
        "answer": "けんり"
    },
    {
        "question": "加わる",
        "answer": "くわわる"
    },
    {
        "question": "神経",
        "answer": "しんけい"
    },
    {
        "question": "差",
        "answer": "さ"
    },
    {
        "question": "明確",
        "answer": "めいかく"
    },
    {
        "question": "収穫",
        "answer": "しゅうかく"
    },
    {
        "question": "議会",
        "answer": "ぎかい"
    },
    {
        "question": "実現",
        "answer": "じつげん"
    },
    {
        "question": "市場",
        "answer": "いちば"
    },
    {
        "question": "王",
        "answer": "おう"
    },
    {
        "question": "職",
        "answer": "しょく"
    },
    {
        "question": "会合",
        "answer": "かいごう"
    },
    {
        "question": "気候",
        "answer": "きこう"
    },
    {
        "question": "変化",
        "answer": "へんか"
    },
    {
        "question": "値",
        "answer": "ね"
    },
    {
        "question": "場面",
        "answer": "ばめん"
    },
    {
        "question": "依頼",
        "answer": "いらい"
    },
    {
        "question": "申し訳",
        "answer": "もうしわけ"
    },
    {
        "question": "全国",
        "answer": "ぜんこく"
    },
    {
        "question": "陽気",
        "answer": "ようき"
    },
    {
        "question": "演技",
        "answer": "えんぎ"
    },
    {
        "question": "責任",
        "answer": "せきにん"
    },
    {
        "question": "任せる",
        "answer": "まかせる"
    },
    {
        "question": "教師",
        "answer": "きょうし"
    },
    {
        "question": "笑い",
        "answer": "わらい"
    },
    {
        "question": "取れる",
        "answer": "とれる"
    },
    {
        "question": "程",
        "answer": "ほど"
    },
    {
        "question": "支出",
        "answer": "ししゅつ"
    },
    {
        "question": "招待",
        "answer": "しょうたい"
    },
    {
        "question": "方向",
        "answer": "ほうこう"
    },
    {
        "question": "演奏",
        "answer": "えんそう"
    },
    {
        "question": "異常",
        "answer": "いじょう"
    },
    {
        "question": "公平",
        "answer": "こうへい"
    },
    {
        "question": "申し込む",
        "answer": "もうしこむ"
    },
    {
        "question": "日光",
        "answer": "にっこう"
    },
    {
        "question": "役割",
        "answer": "やくわり"
    },
    {
        "question": "頂上",
        "answer": "ちょうじょう"
    },
    {
        "question": "余裕",
        "answer": "よゆう"
    },
    {
        "question": "冒険",
        "answer": "ぼうけん"
    },
    {
        "question": "需要",
        "answer": "じゅよう"
    },
    {
        "question": "想像",
        "answer": "そうぞう"
    },
    {
        "question": "続き",
        "answer": "つづき"
    },
    {
        "question": "制限",
        "answer": "せいげん"
    },
    {
        "question": "恐れる",
        "answer": "おそれる"
    },
    {
        "question": "担当",
        "answer": "たんとう"
    },
    {
        "question": "天候",
        "answer": "てんこう"
    },
    {
        "question": "現実",
        "answer": "げんじつ"
    },
    {
        "question": "全然",
        "answer": "ぜんぜん"
    },
    {
        "question": "余り",
        "answer": "あまり"
    },
    {
        "question": "抜く",
        "answer": "ぬく"
    },
    {
        "question": "感じる",
        "answer": "かんじる"
    },
    {
        "question": "禁煙",
        "answer": "きんえん"
    },
    {
        "question": "進歩",
        "answer": "しんぽ"
    },
    {
        "question": "幸い",
        "answer": "さいわい"
    },
    {
        "question": "加減",
        "answer": "かげん"
    },
    {
        "question": "歓迎",
        "answer": "かんげい"
    },
    {
        "question": "女王",
        "answer": "じょおう"
    },
    {
        "question": "都市",
        "answer": "とし"
    },
    {
        "question": "原",
        "answer": "はら"
    },
    {
        "question": "様々",
        "answer": "さまざま"
    },
    {
        "question": "性",
        "answer": "せい"
    },
    {
        "question": "供給",
        "answer": "きょうきゅう"
    },
    {
        "question": "残り",
        "answer": "のこり"
    },
    {
        "question": "全く",
        "answer": "まったく"
    },
    {
        "question": "定期",
        "answer": "ていき"
    },
    {
        "question": "能力",
        "answer": "のうりょく"
    },
    {
        "question": "断る",
        "answer": "ことわる"
    },
    {
        "question": "現す",
        "answer": "あらわす"
    },
    {
        "question": "勘定",
        "answer": "かんじょう"
    },
    {
        "question": "酒",
        "answer": "さけ"
    },
    {
        "question": "家具",
        "answer": "かぐ"
    },
    {
        "question": "現場",
        "answer": "げんば"
    },
    {
        "question": "就職",
        "answer": "しゅうしょく"
    },
    {
        "question": "種",
        "answer": "たね"
    },
    {
        "question": "機嫌",
        "answer": "きげん"
    },
    {
        "question": "好む",
        "answer": "このむ"
    },
    {
        "question": "判断",
        "answer": "はんだん"
    },
    {
        "question": "予測",
        "answer": "よそく"
    },
    {
        "question": "情報",
        "answer": "じょうほう"
    },
    {
        "question": "見舞い",
        "answer": "みまい"
    },
    {
        "question": "経つ",
        "answer": "たつ"
    },
    {
        "question": "観客",
        "answer": "かんきゃく"
    },
    {
        "question": "加える",
        "answer": "くわえる"
    },
    {
        "question": "放送",
        "answer": "ほうそう"
    },
    {
        "question": "記念",
        "answer": "きねん"
    },
    {
        "question": "頼る",
        "answer": "たよる"
    },
    {
        "question": "人類",
        "answer": "じんるい"
    },
    {
        "question": "最高",
        "answer": "さいこう"
    },
    {
        "question": "処理",
        "answer": "しょり"
    },
    {
        "question": "婚約",
        "answer": "こんやく"
    },
    {
        "question": "守る",
        "answer": "まもる"
    },
    {
        "question": "進学",
        "answer": "しんがく"
    },
    {
        "question": "記憶",
        "answer": "きおく"
    },
    {
        "question": "都会",
        "answer": "とかい"
    },
    {
        "question": "理解",
        "answer": "りかい"
    },
    {
        "question": "付ける",
        "answer": "つける"
    },
    {
        "question": "模様",
        "answer": "もよう"
    },
    {
        "question": "通り過ぎる",
        "answer": "とおりすぎる"
    },
    {
        "question": "表面",
        "answer": "ひょうめん"
    },
    {
        "question": "向く",
        "answer": "むく"
    },
    {
        "question": "引退",
        "answer": "いんたい"
    },
    {
        "question": "呼吸",
        "answer": "こきゅう"
    },
    {
        "question": "疑う",
        "answer": "うたがう"
    },
    {
        "question": "命令",
        "answer": "めいれい"
    },
    {
        "question": "要するに",
        "answer": "ようするに"
    },
    {
        "question": "救助",
        "answer": "きゅうじょ"
    },
    {
        "question": "追い付く",
        "answer": "おいつく"
    },
    {
        "question": "飛行",
        "answer": "ひこう"
    },
    {
        "question": "限る",
        "answer": "かぎる"
    },
    {
        "question": "現れる",
        "answer": "あらわれる"
    },
    {
        "question": "幾つ",
        "answer": "いくつ"
    },
    {
        "question": "犯人",
        "answer": "はんにん"
    },
    {
        "question": "時刻",
        "answer": "じこく"
    },
    {
        "question": "地平線",
        "answer": "ちへいせん"
    },
    {
        "question": "義務",
        "answer": "ぎむ"
    },
    {
        "question": "完全",
        "answer": "かんぜん"
    },
    {
        "question": "好み",
        "answer": "このみ"
    },
    {
        "question": "安定",
        "answer": "あんてい"
    },
    {
        "question": "苦手",
        "answer": "にがて"
    },
    {
        "question": "便り",
        "answer": "たより"
    },
    {
        "question": "見当",
        "answer": "けんとう"
    },
    {
        "question": "精々",
        "answer": "せいぜい"
    },
    {
        "question": "衝突",
        "answer": "しょうとつ"
    },
    {
        "question": "婦人",
        "answer": "ふじん"
    },
    {
        "question": "表",
        "answer": "ひょう"
    },
    {
        "question": "観察",
        "answer": "かんさつ"
    },
    {
        "question": "平等",
        "answer": "びょうどう"
    },
    {
        "question": "連想",
        "answer": "れんそう"
    },
    {
        "question": "向ける",
        "answer": "むける"
    },
    {
        "question": "年寄",
        "answer": "としより"
    },
    {
        "question": "疲れ",
        "answer": "つかれ"
    },
    {
        "question": "資源",
        "answer": "しげん"
    },
    {
        "question": "感心",
        "answer": "かんしん"
    },
    {
        "question": "存在",
        "answer": "そんざい"
    },
    {
        "question": "時期",
        "answer": "じき"
    },
    {
        "question": "手術",
        "answer": "しゅじゅつ"
    },
    {
        "question": "苦しい",
        "answer": "くるしい"
    },
    {
        "question": "背",
        "answer": "せい"
    },
    {
        "question": "発達",
        "answer": "はったつ"
    },
    {
        "question": "信頼",
        "answer": "しんらい"
    },
    {
        "question": "迷子",
        "answer": "まいご"
    },
    {
        "question": "準備",
        "answer": "じゅんび"
    },
    {
        "question": "現象",
        "answer": "げんしょう"
    },
    {
        "question": "否定",
        "answer": "ひてい"
    },
    {
        "question": "人込み",
        "answer": "ひとごみ"
    },
    {
        "question": "真似",
        "answer": "まね"
    },
    {
        "question": "実行",
        "answer": "じっこう"
    },
    {
        "question": "倒す",
        "answer": "たおす"
    },
    {
        "question": "逮捕",
        "answer": "たいほ"
    },
    {
        "question": "裁判",
        "answer": "さいばん"
    },
    {
        "question": "舞台",
        "answer": "ぶたい"
    },
    {
        "question": "調査",
        "answer": "ちょうさ"
    },
    {
        "question": "誤り",
        "answer": "あやまり"
    },
    {
        "question": "構成",
        "answer": "こうせい"
    },
    {
        "question": "備える",
        "answer": "そなえる"
    },
    {
        "question": "優秀",
        "answer": "ゆうしゅう"
    },
    {
        "question": "関心",
        "answer": "かんしん"
    },
    {
        "question": "暮らし",
        "answer": "くらし"
    },
    {
        "question": "他",
        "answer": "た"
    },
    {
        "question": "思想",
        "answer": "しそう"
    },
    {
        "question": "有利",
        "answer": "ゆうり"
    },
    {
        "question": "作曲",
        "answer": "さっきょく"
    },
    {
        "question": "選手",
        "answer": "せんしゅ"
    },
    {
        "question": "絶滅",
        "answer": "ぜつめつ"
    },
    {
        "question": "全て",
        "answer": "すべて"
    },
    {
        "question": "偶然",
        "answer": "ぐうぜん"
    },
    {
        "question": "俳優",
        "answer": "はいゆう"
    },
    {
        "question": "助手",
        "answer": "じょしゅ"
    },
    {
        "question": "最終",
        "answer": "さいしゅう"
    },
    {
        "question": "割る",
        "answer": "わる"
    },
    {
        "question": "礼儀",
        "answer": "れいぎ"
    },
    {
        "question": "全体",
        "answer": "ぜんたい"
    },
    {
        "question": "真面目",
        "answer": "まじめ"
    },
    {
        "question": "経営",
        "answer": "けいえい"
    },
    {
        "question": "違いない",
        "answer": "ちがいない"
    },
    {
        "question": "幸運",
        "answer": "こううん"
    },
    {
        "question": "失う",
        "answer": "うしなう"
    },
    {
        "question": "流れる",
        "answer": "ながれる"
    },
    {
        "question": "犯罪",
        "answer": "はんざい"
    },
    {
        "question": "許可",
        "answer": "きょか"
    },
    {
        "question": "活気",
        "answer": "かっき"
    },
    {
        "question": "豊富",
        "answer": "ほうふ"
    },
    {
        "question": "土産",
        "answer": "みやげ"
    },
    {
        "question": "微笑む",
        "answer": "ほほえむ"
    },
    {
        "question": "意識",
        "answer": "いしき"
    },
    {
        "question": "過ごす",
        "answer": "すごす"
    },
    {
        "question": "利益",
        "answer": "りえき"
    },
    {
        "question": "労働",
        "answer": "ろうどう"
    },
    {
        "question": "正直",
        "answer": "しょうじき"
    },
    {
        "question": "感情",
        "answer": "かんじょう"
    },
    {
        "question": "吸収",
        "answer": "きゅうしゅう"
    },
    {
        "question": "留める",
        "answer": "とめる"
    },
    {
        "question": "愛情",
        "answer": "あいじょう"
    },
    {
        "question": "戦い",
        "answer": "たたかい"
    },
    {
        "question": "苦しむ",
        "answer": "くるしむ"
    },
    {
        "question": "数字",
        "answer": "すうじ"
    },
    {
        "question": "当てる",
        "answer": "あてる"
    },
    {
        "question": "合図",
        "answer": "あいず"
    },
    {
        "question": "不平",
        "answer": "ふへい"
    },
    {
        "question": "内容",
        "answer": "ないよう"
    },
    {
        "question": "煙",
        "answer": "けむり"
    },
    {
        "question": "欠点",
        "answer": "けってん"
    },
    {
        "question": "覚ます",
        "answer": "さます"
    },
    {
        "question": "破産",
        "answer": "はさん"
    },
    {
        "question": "観光",
        "answer": "かんこう"
    },
    {
        "question": "格好",
        "answer": "かっこう"
    },
    {
        "question": "光景",
        "answer": "こうけい"
    },
    {
        "question": "現在",
        "answer": "げんざい"
    },
    {
        "question": "満ちる",
        "answer": "みちる"
    },
    {
        "question": "未だ",
        "answer": "まだ"
    },
    {
        "question": "性格",
        "answer": "せいかく"
    },
    {
        "question": "論じる",
        "answer": "ろんじる"
    },
    {
        "question": "苦痛",
        "answer": "くつう"
    },
    {
        "question": "前進",
        "answer": "ぜんしん"
    },
    {
        "question": "事実",
        "answer": "じじつ"
    },
    {
        "question": "弁当",
        "answer": "べんとう"
    },
    {
        "question": "苦労",
        "answer": "くろう"
    },
    {
        "question": "掃除",
        "answer": "そうじ"
    },
    {
        "question": "彼等",
        "answer": "かれら"
    },
    {
        "question": "食欲",
        "answer": "しょくよく"
    },
    {
        "question": "単語",
        "answer": "たんご"
    },
    {
        "question": "解ける",
        "answer": "とける"
    },
    {
        "question": "降ろす",
        "answer": "おろす"
    },
    {
        "question": "解決",
        "answer": "かいけつ"
    },
    {
        "question": "平均",
        "answer": "へいきん"
    },
    {
        "question": "信じる",
        "answer": "しんじる"
    },
    {
        "question": "都",
        "answer": "みやこ"
    },
    {
        "question": "引っ張る",
        "answer": "ひっぱる"
    },
    {
        "question": "回す",
        "answer": "まわす"
    },
    {
        "question": "急速",
        "answer": "きゅうそく"
    },
    {
        "question": "価値",
        "answer": "かち"
    },
    {
        "question": "指す",
        "answer": "さす"
    },
    {
        "question": "正確",
        "answer": "せいかく"
    },
    {
        "question": "心配",
        "answer": "しんぱい"
    },
    {
        "question": "高速",
        "answer": "こうそく"
    },
    {
        "question": "混雑",
        "answer": "こんざつ"
    },
    {
        "question": "支払う",
        "answer": "しはらう"
    },
    {
        "question": "保存",
        "answer": "ほぞん"
    },
    {
        "question": "主要",
        "answer": "しゅよう"
    },
    {
        "question": "共通",
        "answer": "きょうつう"
    },
    {
        "question": "馬",
        "answer": "うま"
    },
    {
        "question": "不利",
        "answer": "ふり"
    },
    {
        "question": "横断",
        "answer": "おうだん"
    },
    {
        "question": "組合",
        "answer": "くみあい"
    },
    {
        "question": "全員",
        "answer": "ぜんいん"
    },
    {
        "question": "御",
        "answer": "お"
    },
    {
        "question": "信仰",
        "answer": "しんこう"
    },
    {
        "question": "医師",
        "answer": "いし"
    },
    {
        "question": "事情",
        "answer": "じじょう"
    },
    {
        "question": "損害",
        "answer": "そんがい"
    },
    {
        "question": "非常",
        "answer": "ひじょう"
    },
    {
        "question": "適する",
        "answer": "てきする"
    },
    {
        "question": "閉じる",
        "answer": "とじる"
    },
    {
        "question": "商人",
        "answer": "しょうにん"
    },
    {
        "question": "負け",
        "answer": "まけ"
    },
    {
        "question": "暮らす",
        "answer": "くらす"
    },
    {
        "question": "実施",
        "answer": "じっし"
    },
    {
        "question": "増す",
        "answer": "ます"
    },
    {
        "question": "戻す",
        "answer": "もどす"
    },
    {
        "question": "礼",
        "answer": "れい"
    },
    {
        "question": "順調",
        "answer": "じゅんちょう"
    },
    {
        "question": "速度",
        "answer": "そくど"
    },
    {
        "question": "居眠り",
        "answer": "いねむり"
    },
    {
        "question": "大戦",
        "answer": "たいせん"
    },
    {
        "question": "利口",
        "answer": "りこう"
    },
    {
        "question": "掲示",
        "answer": "けいじ"
    },
    {
        "question": "役",
        "answer": "やく"
    },
    {
        "question": "地球",
        "answer": "ちきゅう"
    },
    {
        "question": "居る",
        "answer": "おる"
    },
    {
        "question": "熱心",
        "answer": "ねっしん"
    },
    {
        "question": "成功",
        "answer": "せいこう"
    },
    {
        "question": "恐怖",
        "answer": "きょうふ"
    },
    {
        "question": "要素",
        "answer": "ようそ"
    },
    {
        "question": "乗せる",
        "answer": "のせる"
    },
    {
        "question": "流行",
        "answer": "りゅうこう"
    },
    {
        "question": "未来",
        "answer": "みらい"
    },
    {
        "question": "感じ",
        "answer": "かんじ"
    },
    {
        "question": "不満",
        "answer": "ふまん"
    },
    {
        "question": "理想",
        "answer": "りそう"
    },
    {
        "question": "冷静",
        "answer": "れいせい"
    },
    {
        "question": "芸術",
        "answer": "げいじゅつ"
    },
    {
        "question": "流す",
        "answer": "ながす"
    },
    {
        "question": "残す",
        "answer": "のこす"
    },
    {
        "question": "過去",
        "answer": "かこ"
    },
    {
        "question": "繰り返す",
        "answer": "くりかえす"
    },
    {
        "question": "反抗",
        "answer": "はんこう"
    },
    {
        "question": "捕まる",
        "answer": "つかまる"
    },
    {
        "question": "手伝い",
        "answer": "てつだい"
    },
    {
        "question": "宿",
        "answer": "やど"
    },
    {
        "question": "論文",
        "answer": "ろんぶん"
    },
    {
        "question": "差別",
        "answer": "さべつ"
    },
    {
        "question": "設備",
        "answer": "せつび"
    },
    {
        "question": "勿論",
        "answer": "もちろん"
    },
    {
        "question": "付き合い",
        "answer": "つきあい"
    },
    {
        "question": "審判",
        "answer": "しんぱん"
    },
    {
        "question": "悲しむ",
        "answer": "かなしむ"
    },
    {
        "question": "虫歯",
        "answer": "むしば"
    },
    {
        "question": "確かめる",
        "answer": "たしかめる"
    },
    {
        "question": "務め",
        "answer": "つとめ"
    },
    {
        "question": "広告",
        "answer": "こうこく"
    },
    {
        "question": "追う",
        "answer": "おう"
    },
    {
        "question": "誤解",
        "answer": "ごかい"
    },
    {
        "question": "参加",
        "answer": "さんか"
    },
    {
        "question": "失望",
        "answer": "しつぼう"
    },
    {
        "question": "活動",
        "answer": "かつどう"
    },
    {
        "question": "主婦",
        "answer": "しゅふ"
    },
    {
        "question": "感謝",
        "answer": "かんしゃ"
    },
    {
        "question": "平和",
        "answer": "へいわ"
    },
    {
        "question": "講演",
        "answer": "こうえん"
    },
    {
        "question": "財産",
        "answer": "ざいさん"
    },
    {
        "question": "幸せ",
        "answer": "しあわせ"
    },
    {
        "question": "登山",
        "answer": "とざん"
    },
    {
        "question": "欠席",
        "answer": "けっせき"
    },
    {
        "question": "議論",
        "answer": "ぎろん"
    },
    {
        "question": "命じる",
        "answer": "めいじる"
    },
    {
        "question": "予算",
        "answer": "よさん"
    },
    {
        "question": "商売",
        "answer": "しょうばい"
    },
    {
        "question": "回復",
        "answer": "かいふく"
    },
    {
        "question": "条件",
        "answer": "じょうけん"
    },
    {
        "question": "結局",
        "answer": "けっきょく"
    },
    {
        "question": "実際",
        "answer": "じっさい"
    },
    {
        "question": "望む",
        "answer": "のぞむ"
    },
    {
        "question": "承認",
        "answer": "しょうにん"
    },
    {
        "question": "期待",
        "answer": "きたい"
    },
    {
        "question": "大部分",
        "answer": "だいぶぶん"
    },
    {
        "question": "通過",
        "answer": "つうか"
    },
    {
        "question": "喜び",
        "answer": "よろこび"
    },
    {
        "question": "景気",
        "answer": "けいき"
    },
    {
        "question": "求める",
        "answer": "もとめる"
    },
    {
        "question": "実",
        "answer": "み"
    },
    {
        "question": "免許",
        "answer": "めんきょ"
    },
    {
        "question": "乗客",
        "answer": "じょうきゃく"
    },
    {
        "question": "違い",
        "answer": "ちがい"
    },
    {
        "question": "向かい",
        "answer": "むかい"
    },
    {
        "question": "石炭",
        "answer": "せきたん"
    },
    {
        "question": "勝ち",
        "answer": "かち"
    },
    {
        "question": "現代",
        "answer": "げんだい"
    },
    {
        "question": "太陽",
        "answer": "たいよう"
    },
    {
        "question": "遅刻",
        "answer": "ちこく"
    },
    {
        "question": "話し合う",
        "answer": "はなしあう"
    },
    {
        "question": "船",
        "answer": "ふね"
    },
    {
        "question": "進める",
        "answer": "すすめる"
    },
    {
        "question": "職業",
        "answer": "しょくぎょう"
    },
    {
        "question": "全",
        "answer": "ぜん"
    },
    {
        "question": "予報",
        "answer": "よほう"
    },
    {
        "question": "相当",
        "answer": "そうとう"
    },
    {
        "question": "法",
        "answer": "ほう"
    },
    {
        "question": "当時",
        "answer": "とうじ"
    },
    {
        "question": "強調",
        "answer": "きょうちょう"
    },
    {
        "question": "居間",
        "answer": "いま"
    },
    {
        "question": "単純",
        "answer": "たんじゅん"
    },
    {
        "question": "髪の毛",
        "answer": "かみのけ"
    },
    {
        "question": "頂く",
        "answer": "いただく"
    },
    {
        "question": "様子",
        "answer": "ようす"
    },
    {
        "question": "結果",
        "answer": "けっか"
    },
    {
        "question": "精神",
        "answer": "せいしん"
    },
    {
        "question": "暮れ",
        "answer": "くれ"
    },
    {
        "question": "援助",
        "answer": "えんじょ"
    },
    {
        "question": "突然",
        "answer": "とつぜん"
    },
    {
        "question": "更に",
        "answer": "さらに"
    },
    {
        "question": "本当",
        "answer": "ほんと"
    },
    {
        "question": "支払",
        "answer": "しはらい"
    },
    {
        "question": "順番",
        "answer": "じゅんばん"
    },
    {
        "question": "得る",
        "answer": "える"
    },
    {
        "question": "学期",
        "answer": "がっき"
    },
    {
        "question": "王子",
        "answer": "おうじ"
    },
    {
        "question": "感覚",
        "answer": "かんかく"
    },
    {
        "question": "罪",
        "answer": "つみ"
    },
    {
        "question": "郵便",
        "answer": "ゆうびん"
    },
    {
        "question": "単に",
        "answer": "たんに"
    },
    {
        "question": "相談",
        "answer": "そうだん"
    },
    {
        "question": "段",
        "answer": "だん"
    },
    {
        "question": "発表",
        "answer": "はっぴょう"
    },
    {
        "question": "実は",
        "answer": "じつは"
    },
    {
        "question": "当たる",
        "answer": "あたる"
    },
    {
        "question": "助ける",
        "answer": "たすける"
    },
    {
        "question": "給料",
        "answer": "きゅうりょう"
    },
    {
        "question": "支える",
        "answer": "ささえる"
    },
    {
        "question": "済ませる",
        "answer": "すませる"
    },
    {
        "question": "住民",
        "answer": "じゅうみん"
    },
    {
        "question": "回",
        "answer": "かい"
    },
    {
        "question": "他人",
        "answer": "たにん"
    },
    {
        "question": "女優",
        "answer": "じょゆう"
    },
    {
        "question": "様",
        "answer": "よう"
    },
    {
        "question": "収める",
        "answer": "おさめる"
    },
    {
        "question": "請求",
        "answer": "せいきゅう"
    },
    {
        "question": "政府",
        "answer": "せいふ"
    },
    {
        "question": "最も",
        "answer": "もっとも"
    },
    {
        "question": "通信",
        "answer": "つうしん"
    },
    {
        "question": "永遠",
        "answer": "えいえん"
    },
    {
        "question": "迎え",
        "answer": "むかえ"
    },
    {
        "question": "死亡",
        "answer": "しぼう"
    },
    {
        "question": "必死",
        "answer": "ひっし"
    },
    {
        "question": "対",
        "answer": "たい"
    },
    {
        "question": "有能",
        "answer": "ゆうのう"
    },
    {
        "question": "組織",
        "answer": "そしき"
    },
    {
        "question": "常に",
        "answer": "つねに"
    },
    {
        "question": "予防",
        "answer": "よぼう"
    },
    {
        "question": "技師",
        "answer": "ぎし"
    },
    {
        "question": "優勝",
        "answer": "ゆうしょう"
    },
    {
        "question": "次第",
        "answer": "しだい"
    },
    {
        "question": "流れ",
        "answer": "ながれ"
    },
    {
        "question": "外交",
        "answer": "がいこう"
    },
    {
        "question": "自然",
        "answer": "しぜん"
    },
    {
        "question": "論争",
        "answer": "ろんそう"
    },
    {
        "question": "症状",
        "answer": "しょうじょう"
    },
    {
        "question": "警告",
        "answer": "けいこく"
    },
    {
        "question": "泳ぎ",
        "answer": "およぎ"
    },
    {
        "question": "要点",
        "answer": "ようてん"
    },
    {
        "question": "遠慮",
        "answer": "えんりょ"
    },
    {
        "question": "資本",
        "answer": "しほん"
    },
    {
        "question": "装置",
        "answer": "そうち"
    },
    {
        "question": "お腹",
        "answer": "おなか"
    },
    {
        "question": "等しい",
        "answer": "ひとしい"
    },
    {
        "question": "留学",
        "answer": "りゅうがく"
    },
    {
        "question": "息",
        "answer": "いき"
    },
    {
        "question": "束",
        "answer": "たば"
    },
    {
        "question": "勤め",
        "answer": "つとめ"
    },
    {
        "question": "代表",
        "answer": "だいひょう"
    },
    {
        "question": "日常",
        "answer": "にちじょう"
    },
    {
        "question": "解く",
        "answer": "とく"
    },
    {
        "question": "容易",
        "answer": "ようい"
    },
    {
        "question": "直ちに",
        "answer": "ただちに"
    },
    {
        "question": "直接",
        "answer": "ちょくせつ"
    },
    {
        "question": "お互い",
        "answer": "おたがい"
    },
    {
        "question": "数える",
        "answer": "かぞえる"
    },
    {
        "question": "書類",
        "answer": "しょるい"
    },
    {
        "question": "寄付",
        "answer": "きふ"
    },
    {
        "question": "投票",
        "answer": "とうひょう"
    },
    {
        "question": "候補",
        "answer": "こうほ"
    },
    {
        "question": "解釈",
        "answer": "かいしゃく"
    },
    {
        "question": "被害",
        "answer": "ひがい"
    },
    {
        "question": "交際",
        "answer": "こうさい"
    },
    {
        "question": "大変",
        "answer": "たいへん"
    },
    {
        "question": "一種",
        "answer": "いっしゅ"
    },
    {
        "question": "球",
        "answer": "きゅう"
    },
    {
        "question": "配達",
        "answer": "はいたつ"
    },
    {
        "question": "共に",
        "answer": "ともに"
    },
    {
        "question": "賛成",
        "answer": "Uӣ[い"
    },
    {
        "question": "決心",
        "answer": "けっしん"
    },
    {
        "question": "夫人",
        "answer": "ふじん"
    },
    {
        "question": "昨",
        "answer": "さく"
    },
    {
        "question": "到着",
        "answer": "とうちゃく"
    },
    {
        "question": "連続",
        "answer": "れんぞく"
    },
    {
        "question": "農民",
        "answer": "のうみん"
    },
    {
        "question": "調子",
        "answer": "ちょうし"
    },
    {
        "question": "余分",
        "answer": "よぶん"
    },
    {
        "question": "適用",
        "answer": "てきよう"
    },
    {
        "question": "完成",
        "answer": "かんせい"
    },
    {
        "question": "報告",
        "answer": "ほうこく"
    },
    {
        "question": "位置",
        "answer": "いち"
    },
    {
        "question": "次々",
        "answer": "つぎつぎ"
    },
    {
        "question": "実に",
        "answer": "じつに"
    },
    {
        "question": "辞める",
        "answer": "やめる"
    },
    {
        "question": "値段",
        "answer": "ねだん"
    },
    {
        "question": "道路",
        "answer": "どうろ"
    },
    {
        "question": "教科書",
        "answer": "きょうかしょ"
    },
    {
        "question": "困難",
        "answer": "こんなん"
    },
    {
        "question": "首相",
        "answer": "しゅしょう"
    },
    {
        "question": "常識",
        "answer": "じょうしき"
    },
    {
        "question": "飛ばす",
        "answer": "とばす"
    },
    {
        "question": "頭痛",
        "answer": "ずつう"
    },
    {
        "question": "与える",
        "answer": "あたえる"
    },
    {
        "question": "抱く",
        "answer": "いだく"
    },
    {
        "question": "部分",
        "answer": "ぶぶん"
    },
    {
        "question": "願う",
        "answer": "ねがう"
    },
    {
        "question": "笑顔",
        "answer": "えがお"
    },
    {
        "question": "商品",
        "answer": "しょうひん"
    },
    {
        "question": "収入",
        "answer": "しゅうにゅう"
    },
    {
        "question": "越える",
        "answer": "こえる"
    },
    {
        "question": "障害",
        "answer": "しょうがい"
    },
    {
        "question": "打つ",
        "answer": "ぶつ"
    },
    {
        "question": "恐ろしい",
        "answer": "おそろしい"
    },
    {
        "question": "例",
        "answer": "れい"
    },
    {
        "question": "現れ",
        "answer": "あらわれ"
    },
    {
        "question": "長期",
        "answer": "ちょうき"
    },
    {
        "question": "偶々",
        "answer": "たまたま"
    },
    {
        "question": "友情",
        "answer": "ゆうじょう"
    },
    {
        "question": "合格",
        "answer": "ごうかく"
    },
    {
        "question": "選択",
        "answer": "せんたく"
    },
    {
        "question": "違反",
        "answer": "いはん"
    },
    {
        "question": "経験",
        "answer": "けいけん"
    },
    {
        "question": "除く",
        "answer": "のぞく"
    },
    {
        "question": "退屈",
        "answer": "たいくつ"
    },
    {
        "question": "共同",
        "answer": "きょうどう"
    },
    {
        "question": "内",
        "answer": "うち"
    },
    {
        "question": "合計",
        "answer": "ごうけい"
    },
    {
        "question": "組",
        "answer": "くみ"
    },
    {
        "question": "等",
        "answer": "など"
    },
    {
        "question": "重要",
        "answer": "じゅうよう"
    },
    {
        "question": "構う",
        "answer": "かまう"
    },
    {
        "question": "生命",
        "answer": "せいめい"
    },
    {
        "question": "記入",
        "answer": "きにゅう"
    },
    {
        "question": "表す",
        "answer": "あらわす"
    },
    {
        "question": "訪問",
        "answer": "ほうもん"
    },
    {
        "question": "強盗",
        "answer": "ごうとう"
    },
    {
        "question": "価格",
        "answer": "かかく"
    },
    {
        "question": "式",
        "answer": "しき"
    },
    {
        "question": "感動",
        "answer": "かんどう"
    },
    {
        "question": "越す",
        "answer": "こす"
    },
    {
        "question": "表現",
        "answer": "ひょうげん"
    },
    {
        "question": "状況",
        "answer": "じょうきょう"
    },
    {
        "question": "粗末",
        "answer": "そまつ"
    },
    {
        "question": "連れ",
        "answer": "つれ"
    },
    {
        "question": "局",
        "answer": "きょく"
    },
    {
        "question": "事件",
        "answer": "じけん"
    },
    {
        "question": "願い",
        "answer": "ねがい"
    },
    {
        "question": "案内",
        "answer": "あんない"
    },
    {
        "question": "幾ら",
        "answer": "いくら"
    },
    {
        "question": "放す",
        "answer": "はなす"
    },
    {
        "question": "今回",
        "answer": "こんかい"
    },
    {
        "question": "支店",
        "answer": "してん"
    },
    {
        "question": "深刻",
        "answer": "しんこく"
    },
    {
        "question": "殺す",
        "answer": "ころす"
    },
    {
        "question": "責める",
        "answer": "せめる"
    },
    {
        "question": "停留所",
        "answer": "ていりゅうじょ"
    },
    {
        "question": "現金",
        "answer": "げんきん"
    },
    {
        "question": "制度",
        "answer": "せいど"
    },
    {
        "question": "事務",
        "answer": "じむ"
    },
    {
        "question": "抱える",
        "answer": "かかえる"
    },
    {
        "question": "決まり",
        "answer": "きまり"
    },
    {
        "question": "間違い",
        "answer": "まちがい"
    },
    {
        "question": "取り上げる",
        "answer": "とりあげる"
    },
    {
        "question": "風景",
        "answer": "ふうけい"
    },
    {
        "question": "信号",
        "answer": "しんごう"
    },
    {
        "question": "望み",
        "answer": "のぞみ"
    },
    {
        "question": "冗談",
        "answer": "じょうだん"
    },
    {
        "question": "生産",
        "answer": "せいさん"
    },
    {
        "question": "優れる",
        "answer": "すぐれる"
    },
    {
        "question": "是非",
        "answer": "ぜひ"
    },
    {
        "question": "愛する",
        "answer": "あいする"
    },
    {
        "question": "積極的",
        "answer": "せっきょくてき"
    },
    {
        "question": "熱中",
        "answer": "ねっちゅう"
    },
    {
        "question": "憲法",
        "answer": "けんぽう"
    },
    {
        "question": "議員",
        "answer": "ぎいん"
    },
    {
        "question": "手段",
        "answer": "しゅだん"
    },
    {
        "question": "王様",
        "answer": "おうさま"
    },
    {
        "question": "機関",
        "answer": "きかん"
    },
    {
        "question": "座席",
        "answer": "ざせき"
    },
    {
        "question": "お目に掛かる",
        "answer": "おめにかかる"
    },
    {
        "question": "機能",
        "answer": "きのう"
    },
    {
        "question": "覚める",
        "answer": "さめる"
    },
    {
        "question": "抜ける",
        "answer": "ぬける"
    },
    {
        "question": "神",
        "answer": "かみ"
    },
    {
        "question": "延期",
        "answer": "えんき"
    },
    {
        "question": "体育",
        "answer": "たいいく"
    },
    {
        "question": "必ずしも",
        "answer": "かならずしも"
    },
    {
        "question": "幸福",
        "answer": "こうふく"
    },
    {
        "question": "腹",
        "answer": "はら"
    },
    {
        "question": "可能",
        "answer": "かのう"
    },
    {
        "question": "適度",
        "answer": "てきど"
    },
    {
        "question": "具体",
        "answer": "ぐたい"
    },
    {
        "question": "日付",
        "answer": "ひづけ"
    },
    {
        "question": "天然",
        "answer": "てんねん"
    },
    {
        "question": "害",
        "answer": "がい"
    },
    {
        "question": "対象",
        "answer": "たいしょう"
    },
    {
        "question": "絶対",
        "answer": "ぜったい"
    },
    {
        "question": "能",
        "answer": "のう"
    },
    {
        "question": "得意",
        "answer": "とくい"
    },
    {
        "question": "暗記",
        "answer": "あんき"
    },
    {
        "question": "満足",
        "answer": "まんぞく"
    },
    {
        "question": "示す",
        "answer": "しめす"
    },
    {
        "question": "偉大",
        "answer": "いだい"
    },
    {
        "question": "記録",
        "answer": "きろく"
    },
    {
        "question": "認める",
        "answer": "みとめる"
    },
    {
        "question": "自殺",
        "answer": "じさつ"
    },
    {
        "question": "関する",
        "answer": "かんする"
    },
    {
        "question": "平ら",
        "answer": "たいら"
    },
    {
        "question": "命",
        "answer": "いのち"
    },
    {
        "question": "予期",
        "answer": "よき"
    },
    {
        "question": "引用",
        "answer": "いんよう"
    },
    {
        "question": "約",
        "answer": "やく"
    },
    {
        "question": "不幸",
        "answer": "ふこう"
    },
    {
        "question": "伝統",
        "answer": "でんとう"
    },
    {
        "question": "経由",
        "answer": "けいゆ"
    },
    {
        "question": "美人",
        "answer": "びじん"
    },
    {
        "question": "否",
        "answer": "いや"
    },
    {
        "question": "知能",
        "answer": "ちのう"
    },
    {
        "question": "完了",
        "answer": "かんりょう"
    },
    {
        "question": "結論",
        "answer": "けつろん"
    },
    {
        "question": "離婚",
        "answer": "りこん"
    },
    {
        "question": "単なる",
        "answer": "たんなる"
    },
    {
        "question": "互い",
        "answer": "たがい"
    },
    {
        "question": "睡眠",
        "answer": "すいみん"
    },
    {
        "question": "快適",
        "answer": "かいてき"
    },
    {
        "question": "消防",
        "answer": "しょうぼう"
    },
    {
        "question": "馬鹿",
        "answer": "ばか"
    },
    {
        "question": "参考",
        "answer": "さんこう"
    },
    {
        "question": "戦う",
        "answer": "たたかう"
    },
    {
        "question": "状態",
        "answer": "じょうたい"
    },
    {
        "question": "診察",
        "answer": "しんさつ"
    },
    {
        "question": "一番",
        "answer": "いちばん"
    },
    {
        "question": "確実",
        "answer": "かくじつ"
    },
    {
        "question": "希望",
        "answer": "きぼう"
    },
    {
        "question": "活用",
        "answer": "かつよう"
    },
    {
        "question": "働き",
        "answer": "はたらき"
    },
    {
        "question": "信用",
        "answer": "しんよう"
    },
    {
        "question": "掛かる",
        "answer": "かかる"
    },
    {
        "question": "側",
        "answer": "そば"
    },
    {
        "question": "傾向",
        "answer": "けいこう"
    },
    {
        "question": "両替",
        "answer": "りょうがえ"
    },
    {
        "question": "評判",
        "answer": "ひょうばん"
    },
    {
        "question": "関連",
        "answer": "かんれん"
    },
    {
        "question": "契約",
        "answer": "けいやく"
    },
    {
        "question": "夢中",
        "answer": "むちゅう"
    },
    {
        "question": "不思議",
        "answer": "ふしぎ"
    },
    {
        "question": "最低",
        "answer": "さいてい"
    },
    {
        "question": "首都",
        "answer": "しゅと"
    },
    {
        "question": "上達",
        "answer": "じょうたつ"
    },
    {
        "question": "記者",
        "answer": "きしゃ"
    },
    {
        "question": "許す",
        "answer": "ゆるす"
    },
    {
        "question": "限界",
        "answer": "げんかい"
    },
    {
        "question": "偶",
        "answer": "たま"
    },
    {
        "question": "際",
        "answer": "さい"
    },
    {
        "question": "横切る",
        "answer": "よこぎる"
    },
    {
        "question": "成績",
        "answer": "せいせき"
    },
    {
        "question": "石油",
        "answer": "せきゆ"
    },
    {
        "question": "支度",
        "answer": "したく"
    },
    {
        "question": "要求",
        "answer": "ようきゅう"
    },
    {
        "question": "成る",
        "answer": "なる"
    },
    {
        "question": "達する",
        "answer": "たっする"
    },
    {
        "question": "不自由",
        "answer": "ふじゆう"
    },
    {
        "question": "欠ける",
        "answer": "かける"
    },
    {
        "question": "直",
        "answer": "じき"
    },
    {
        "question": "支配",
        "answer": "しはい"
    },
    {
        "question": "現状",
        "answer": "げんじょう"
    },
    {
        "question": "列車",
        "answer": "れっしゃ"
    },
    {
        "question": "所為",
        "answer": "せい"
    },
    {
        "question": "成人",
        "answer": "せいじん"
    },
    {
        "question": "表情",
        "answer": "ひょうじょう"
    },
    {
        "question": "種類",
        "answer": "しゅるい"
    },
    {
        "question": "単位",
        "answer": "たんい"
    },
    {
        "question": "滞在",
        "answer": "たいざい"
    },
    {
        "question": "破る",
        "answer": "やぶる"
    },
    {
        "question": "効果",
        "answer": "こうか"
    },
    {
        "question": "決定",
        "answer": "けってい"
    },
    {
        "question": "作法",
        "answer": "さほう"
    },
    {
        "question": "人種",
        "answer": "じんしゅ"
    },
    {
        "question": "宿泊",
        "answer": "しゅくはく"
    },
    {
        "question": "夫婦",
        "answer": "ふうふ"
    },
    {
        "question": "演説",
        "answer": "えんぜつ"
    },
    {
        "question": "説",
        "answer": "せつ"
    }
]